Guide to the Emil J. Dillon Papers, ca. 1873-1933
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Correspondence
  - Subseries 1. Letters, Telegrams, and Related Notes
    - Sonnino, Sidney1911 April 8 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Spender, J.A.1905 June 21 - 1906 Feb. 26 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Spielmann, J. [1 of 2]1892 Oct. 17 - 1893 Feb. 7, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 26, Folder 26)
      Contains materials relating to Mr. E.B. Lanin, Esq.
    - Spielmann, J. [2 of 2]1893 Feb. 12 - August 9, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Spring-Rice, Cecil, Sir [1 of 5]1900 [n.d.] - 1904 Nov. 8, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, als [?], press cuttings. (Box 26, Folder 28)
      Contains materials relating to Kuropatkin; Grand Duke Vladimir; Grand Duke Sergius; Nabokoff; Witte; the Emperor; Mrs. Spring-Rice; Sir Frank Lascelles; Plehve; the Kaiser. Some materials are in Italian.
    - Spring-Rice, Cecil, Sir [2 of 5]1904 June 2 - 1906 August 1, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, als [?], press cuttings. (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Spring-Rice, Cecil, Sir [3 of 5]1907 Nov. 16 - 1909 June 25, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, als [?], press cuttings. (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Spring-Rice, Cecil, Sir [4 of 5]n.d. / n.y., Incl. a descriptive list, tls, als [?], press cuttings. (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Spring-Rice, Cecil, Sir [5 of 5]n.d. / n.y., Incl. a descriptive list, tls, als [?], press cuttings. (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Stambuloff, Stephen1893 April 7 - 1894 Feb. 5 (Box 26, Folder 33)
      Contains materials relating to E.B. Lanin; M. Lowthev. Some materials are in French.
      Stambulov, Stephan
    - Stead, William T. [1 of 13]1889 July 3 - 1890 April 11; n.d., Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Contains materials relating to Arthur Stead; Tolstoi; Madame Novikoff; the Prince of Wales; E.B. Lanin; the Czar [Tsar]; Mrs. Grundy; Gay; Pobedonostseff; General Beoth; the Princess Radzivell [Radziwill]; the wife of General Annenkoff; the Queen of Servia; the Empress of Germany; John Morley; Count Mattei; H.F. Battersby, Esq.; Colonel Durnovo; Mrs. Besant; Mrs. Lynn Linton; Count Taafe; Davitt; Madame Brown; Jack; Emma; Weyler; Don Carlos; Sagasta; Castelar; M. Lessar; Miss Barnicoat; Chamberlain; Alfred; George Hamilton; Mr. Beveredge; Mr. A.H. Kiehl; Mr. Hockstra; Mr. J.H. Altona; Mr. St. Clair; Marquis Ito; Mr. Hofmeyr; Mr. Fischer; General Botha; Dr. Kuypers; the Kaiser; Kruger; Mr. Rawson; Lord Esher; Curzon; Connaught; Kitchener; Sir George Goldie; Miss Noble (Sister Nivadita); Mrs. Creed; Mrs. Campbell; Percy Alden; Charles Morley; Petkovich; Myers; Mr. Spender; Vengeroff; Mr. Hawkes; Mrs. Burchell; M. Louis Melikoff; Mrs. Dillon; Nicolas II; P. Had; Zacherevski; C.S. Parnell; Cecil Spring-Rice; P.N. Miliukoff, Prof.; Witte; Obolenskii; Miss Fox; Herbert Burrows; Mr. Green; Mrs. Minny Olesk; Trepoff; Petrunkeevitch; Shipoff; Shishkoff; Milutin; Colonel Maxie; lamsdorff; Kuropatkin; Mr. Finot; Prince Christopher of Greece; Dr. Macaura; Keats; Mrs. COnstance Grande; Sazonoff; Tcharykoff; Mandelstamn [Mandelshtam ?]. Some materials are in Russian.
    - Stead, William T. [2 of 13]1890 April 14 - July 5; n.d., Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Stead, William T. [3 of 13]1890 August 11 - Oct. 16, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Stead, William T. [4 of 13]1890 Dec. 20 - 1891 Jan. 12; n.d., Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Stead, William T. [5 of 13]1891 Jan. 13 - March 31, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Stead, William T. [6 of 13]1891 July 26 - 1892 Nov. 20, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Stead, William T. [7 of 13]1893 Jan. 30 - 1900 [?] Sept. 7, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Stead, William T. [8 of 13]1900 Jan. 3 - 1902 Oct. 10, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Stead, William T. [9 of 13]1902 Dec. 9 - 1904 May 18, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Stead, William T. [10 of 13]1904 July 16 - 1905 Dec. 19, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Stead, William T. [11 of 13]1906 March 17 - 1909 Dec. 5, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Stead, William T. [12 of 13]1910 May 30 - 1925 May 20, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Stead, William T. [13 of 13]1912 March 21, Incl. press cuttings, tls, als. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Stevenson, F.S.1895 June 29 - 1896 March 13 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Stoop, Bertha1927 [?] [n.d.] (Box 27, Folder 15)
      In English and German.
      Staup, Bertha
    - Streit, G. [?]n.d. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Suqué, [?]1932 Feb. 1, Incl. a typescript. (Box 27, Folder 17)
      Contains materials relating to Miguel Maura; the King; Alcalá Zamorra; Queen-Mother Maria Cristina.
    - Szápáry, Ladislaus, Count1911 Oct. 2 - 1913 April 28, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 27, Folder 18)
      Contains materials relating to Count Aehrenthal; F. Kinsky.
    - Szczepanowski, Stanislav [?]1892 Oct. 13 - 1899 Nov. 20, Incl. postcards. (Box 27, Folder 19)
      Contains materials relating to Taaffe; Hofrath Hofmann; Homer; Jaworski; Dr. Russ. In English and German.
    - Talaat, Bey1914 July 4 - July 14; n.y., Incl. a descriptive list, a menu. (Box 27, Folder 20)
      Contains materials relating to Mrs. Dillon; H. Fehmy Bey Zaim Zadé. Some materials are in French.
      Taléat, Bey
    - Tariverdiev, Abbas-aga1910 July 2 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      Contains materials relating to Vilkoks [?]; Litton.
    - Tevakov [?], Nikolai, Prince1906 Dec. 6; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Tewfyk, Pasha1897 June 26, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 27, Folder 23)
      Tewfik, Pasha
    - Teza, Emilio, Prof.1892 Feb. 7 - 1898 Feb. 14 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Theophilius, F.1887 Jan. 2 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      In Latin and Sanskrit.
    - Thierry, René1915 Dec. 19, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Timiryazeff, Vasilii Ivanovich1909 April 11 / 24; n.d., Incl. a typescript. (Box 27, Folder 27)
      Contains materials relating to P.A. Stolypin; A.P. Izvolskii; V.I. Kokovtsoff; Sir Arthur Nicholson; Sir Albert Spicer; D.J. Morgan, Esq.; Sir Albert K. Pollit; A.A. Geiking, Baron; Henry Cooke; Arthur Woodhouse; Robert Wilton; Henry Wilenskii. One document is in Russian.
      Timiriazeff, Basile De
    - Tittoni, J. [?]1919 [month ?] 11 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Tomich, [?][n.y.] May 11, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 27, Folder 29)
      Contains correspondence in French relating to Olga.
      Tomitch, [?]
    - Toptani, Essad Pasha, General [1 of 3]1914 June 20 - 1916 April 8; n.d., Incl. a press cutting. (Box 27, Folder 30)
      Contains materials relating to President Wilson. Some materials are in French.
    - Toptani, Essad Pasha, General [2 of 3]1916 April 17 - 1917 May 9, Incl. a press cutting. (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Toptani, Essad Pasha, General [3 of 3]1918 Jan. 11 - Sept. 8; n.d., Incl. a press cutting. (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Torreblanco, Fernando1921 Nov. 28; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list, tls. (Box 27, Folder 33)
      Torreblanca, Fernando
    - Touchard, Charles1909 May 27 / April 9 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Tourian, Elisee [?] Evêque1908 Oct. 30, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 27, Folder 35)
      Tourien, Elisee [?] Evêque
    - Trarieux, L.1899 Oct. 6, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Troistorff, W.1874 [Oct. 12 / Dec. 10 ?], Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Troste, [?]n.d. (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Troubetskoi, Lisa, Princess1890 Sept. 10 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Troubetskoy, Lisa, Princess
    - Tun, Francis [?], Count1897 Dec. 14 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Turkhan, [?]n.d., Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Turring, Charles Jenner1894 Dec. 21 - 1895 August 14, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Twain, Markn.d. (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Contains materials relating to Colonel Harvey.
    - Tygoviets [?], E.n.d. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified [1 of 5]1874 [n.d.] - 1895 Nov. 11, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a postcard, a typescript. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Some materials are in French, German, Spanish, and Russian.
    - Unidentified [2 of 5]1904 Dec. 24 - 1920 Feb. 19, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a postcard, a typescript. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified [3 of 5]1920 June 8 - 1926 Dec. 16, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a postcard, a typescript. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified [4 of 5]1930 Jan. 26 - 1932 July 26, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a postcard, a typescript. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified [5 of 5]n.d. / n.y., Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a postcard, a typescript. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Urquidi [?], Juan T. [?] [1 of 2]1921 Oct. 14 - Dec. 26; n.d., Incl. tls. (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Contains materials relating to Mrs. Dillon; the President; Mr. Pani; Mr. Saenz; General Obregón; Mr. Murray; Wolff; Mr. Ricoy [?]; Henry A. Zo; Major C.W. Lowther, M.P.; Mr. T.A. Joyce; Mr. Torreblanca. Some materials are in Spanish.
    - Urquidi [?], Juan T. [?] [2 of 2]1922 Jan. 6 - Nov. 13, Incl. tls. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Val, Alfonso Merry Del.1917 Sept. 22 - 1924 July 9, Incl. tls. (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Contains materials in Spanish relating to Señor Don Eduardo Dato; Señor Marques De Lema.
    - Vámbéry, Armin [?], Prof. [1 of 2]1892 May 28 - 1894 Dec. 25, Incl. als [?]. (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Contains materials relating to Grand Vizier. Some materials are in Hungarian [?].
    - Vámbéry, Armin [?], Prof. [2 of 2]1894 Dec. 31 - 1895 Jan. 4, Incl. als [?]. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Vamvacas [?], Ch., Dr.1913 May 26 - [August ?] 9, Incl. a descriptive list, a press cutting. (Box 28, Folder 17)
      In French and German.
    - Vanderlip, F.A.1921 Nov. 5, Incl. a descriptive list, tls. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Vandervelde, E.1902 April 23 - 1916 June 22 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      Contains materials relating to Calla Vandervelde. One document is in French.
    - Vassos, A., Col. [?]1897 April 8 / 20; n.d. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Vengerov, S.A. [1 of 2]1893 Feb. 9 - 1904 Sept. 20; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a typescript, a postcard. (Box 28, Folder 21)
      Contains materials relating to M. Grinevskii; Stead; Chekhov; Maxim Gorkii. Some materials are in Russian.
      Vengeroff, S.A.; Wengerow, S.A.
    - Vengerov, S.A. [2 of 2]1907 [?] August 26, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a typescript, a postcard. (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Vénisélos, Éleftheros K. [1 of 4]1908 [?] [n.d.] - 1910 Feb. 4; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a typescript, a press cutting. (Box 28, Folder 23)
      Contains materials relating to King George; Sir Francis Elliot; Constantine; Zographos; Grey; Count Mercate; Mr. Keedick; Mr. McClure; Mlle Schilizzi. Some materials are in French.
      Vénizélos, Éleftheros K.
    - Vénisélos, Éleftheros K. [2 of 4]1910 Feb. 7 [?] - 1913 July 9; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a typescript, a press cutting. (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Vénisélos, Éleftheros K. [3 of 4]1914 June 22; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a typescript, a press cutting. (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Vénisélos, Éleftheros K. [4 of 4]1919 Jan. 21 - 192 [7 / 9 ?] July 19; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a typescript, a press cutting. (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Verschoyle, John1891 [?] August 3 - 1902 Oct. 6; n.d. / n.y., Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Viazemski, Dorothea Rosalie1933 June 12 - 1947 May 21, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 28)
      Viazemsky, Dorothea Rosalie; Vyazemsky, Dorothea Rosalie
    - Vigouroux, [M. / F. ?], Abbé1874 Nov. 17 - 1903 Nov. 22, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a card. (Box 28, Folder 29)
      Contains materials relating to Abbé Ancessi, V.; M. Icard. Some materials are in French.
    - Villiers, F.N.1914 April [n.d.] (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Vorontsov-Dashkov, [?], Count1905 April 20 - 1926 Oct. 26, Incl. a descriptive list, tls, a press cutting. (Box 28, Folder 31)
      Contains materials relating to Nol'de, Baron; Mr. Le Sage; M. Dukhovetskii. Some materials are in Russian and German.
      Woronzow, [?], Count; Vorontsoff-Dashkoff, [?], Count
    - Walker, Alan1931 July 14, Tls. (Box 28, Folder 32)
      Contains materials relating to Mrs. Dillon; Luther.
    - Waltrau, [?]1922 April 2, Incl. a descriptive list, tls. (Box 28, Folder 33)
      Waltram, [?]
    - Waring, Mary[1919 ?] Sept. 30, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Warren, N.R.1896 March 11, Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Watts-Dunton, Theodora1899 March 21 - 1907 March 24; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 36)
      Walts [?]-Dunton, Theodora
    - Webb, Beatrice1933 May 2 - May 16; n.d., Incl. tls, a typescript. (Box 28, Folder 37)
      Contains materials relating to Mr. Sidney Webb.
    - Wells, H.G.1921 Dec. 1 - 1932 May 24, Incl. a descriptive list, tls. (Box 28, Folder 38)
      Contains materials relating to John Quinn.
    - Wernekke, [?]1901 Feb. 2 - 1902 Jan. 4, Incl. a descriptive list, a postcard. (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Weyler, [?][1898 ?] n.d., Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 40)
      Weyle [?], [?]
    - Whitlock, Brand1920 Dec. 13, Tls. (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Wilson, W.1899 May 9; n.d., Incl. a descriptive list. (Box 28, Folder 42)
      Contains materials relating to the Pope.
    - Winkler, Hermann [1 of 4]1923 May 2 - 1925 April 14, Incl. tls, typescripts. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Contains materials relating to Dr. Konried; Mexican President; Harriman; Mrs. Dillon; Somary; Pinners; Pi-Sutier; Count Aehrental; Gallieni; Clemenceau; Foch; Poincaré; Professor Schweninger.
    - Winkler, Hermann [2 of 4]1925 July 1 - Sept. 14, Incl. tls, typescripts. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Winkler, Hermann [3 of 4]1932 Nov. 21 - Dec. 9; n.d., Incl. tls, typescripts. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Winkler, Hermann [4 of 4]1932 Dec. 29; n.d., Incl. tls, typescripts. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Wise, Stephen S.1918 Dec. 19, Incl. a descriptive list, tls. (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Contains materials relating to Mrs. Wise.
    - Wiseman, W. [?]1921 July 14, Tls. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Contains materials relating to Mr. Body; Mrs. Dillon.
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1A of 5]1888 Dec. 24 - 1899 March 30; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Contains materials relating to the Tsar; the Kaiser; Trepoff; Lamsdorff; Zakrevskii; Poubedonostseff; Durnovo; Mina Olesk; Protopopoff; Mr. Le Sage; H.L.W. Lawson; Baron Komura; P.A. Stolypin; Kazantseff; Stepanoff; Fiedoroff; Kuropatkin; Pourishkevich; Tolstoi; Azeff; Lopukhine; Urusoff; Lobanoff; Muraviev; V. N. Kokovtsoff; Krivoshein; Boulton; Austin Chamberlain; Lord Morley; Benenson; Shdanoff; Constantine Dillon; the King of Montenegro; Rosenberg; Frischauer; Clemenceau; the King Karl of Roumania; the King Peter of Servia; the Emperor Alexander III; Prince Karageorghevitch; the Dowager Empress; Rasputin; Sazonoff; E.L. Goodman; Iollos; Burtseff; M. Witte; Kovalevskii; Obolenskii; Kotliarevskii; Delcassé; Fachoda; Alphonse Rothschild; Nikolas II; Izvolskii; Krivoshea; Morozoff; Gorkii; Scheglovitoff; Hessen; Bismarck; Morier; Rouvier; Rodolin; Kaufmann; Bulow; Gurko; Polofftseff; Litvinoff; Falinskii; Demidoff; Vorontseff-Dashkoff; Kanikin; Cherevine; Mr. Bunting; Voigt; Heckscher; Pikhno; Kryshenoffskii; Philosoffooff; Kurz; Korostovetz; Schwanebach; Ratenkoffskii; Varlaam, the Bishop of Kargopol; Poliakoff; Varshavskii; Gubonin; Mek-Derviz [?]; Balinskii; Gregorovitch; Marie Pavlova; the Grand Duke Nikolai Mikhailovitch; M. Mitusoff; Madame Vyrybova [Vyrubova ?]; Akimoff; Prince Alexei Dmitri Volkonskii; Poutiloff. Some materials are in French, German, and Russian.
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1B of 5]1900 Feb. 28, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1C of 5]1901 Jan. 26 - Feb. 4 / 17, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1D of 5]1904 Nov. 12 / 25 - 1905 April 17, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1EA of 5]1905 Jan. 25 - 1912 March 20; n.y., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1EB of 5]1905 May 7 - Oct. 1 / 14, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1EC of 5]1905 August 6 - Sept. 19; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1ED of 5]1905 August 15 - Nov. 13, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1EE of 5]1905 Dec. 12 - 1917 Dec. 31; n.d. / n.y., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1EF of 5]n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1EG of 5]n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1FA of 5]1906 March 22 - June 26 [?]; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1FB of 5]1906 April 11 / 24 - May 12; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1FC of 5]1906 June 12 - August 1, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1FD of 5]1906 August 17 - Sept. 28, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1FE of 5]1906 Oct. 1 / 14 - 1907 Feb. 12 / 25; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1FF of 5]1906 Dec. 13; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1FG of 5]n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1GA of 5]1909 Feb. 10 - 1910 May 3, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1GB of 5]1910 Dec. 2 - Dec 16, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1H of 5]1907 May 6 - Nov. 9, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1IA of 5]1908 March 4 / 17 - March 22 / April 4; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1IB of 5]1908 March 15 / 28 - Oct. 17; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1IC of 5]190 [7 / 8 ?] [n.d.] - 1908 Sept. 1, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1ID of 5]1908 Oct. 13 / 26 - Nov. 3 / 16; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1JA of 5]1908 Dec. 23 - 1909 Feb. 14 / 27; n.d. / n.y., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1JB of 5]1909 June 17 / 30 - Sept. 1 [?], Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1JC of 5]1909 Sept. 8 - 1911 [?] June 15, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1KA of 5]1910 June 6 / 19 - Sept. 3, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1KB of 5]1910 August 13 / 26 - Oct. 17, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1KC of 5]1910 Oct. 21 - Nov. 18; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1KD of 5]1910 Nov. 19 - Dec. 5; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1KE of 5]n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1LA of 5]1911 April 16 - August 17, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1LB of 5]1911 August 22 - August 28, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1LC of 5]1911 Sept. 20, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1LD of 5]1911 Oct. 27 - Dec. 16; n.d., Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1M of 5]1912 July 23 / August 5 - August 28, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1NA of 5]1913 April 26 / May 9 - May 15 / 28, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1NB of 5]1913 June 1 - August 29 / Sept. 11, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Witte, Sergei Iulievich, Count [1NC of 5]1913 Sept. 1 / 14 - Sept. 3 / 16, Incl. descriptive lists, press cuttings, als, tls, typescripts, postcards, a photo, books, leaflets. (Box 30, Folder 22)